# anusha narayan

# human-centred design engineer

anusha.narayan2002@outook.com

linkedin.com/in/a-k-narayan

anushanarayan.com

# profile

Third year design engineering student at Imperial College London with a particular interest in human-centred and UX design. Carried out multiple projects, both individually and in teams, working to solve problems affecting particular segments of society. A diligent and enthusiastic team player, very experienced in working within tight time constraints.

### education

# Imperial College London - MEng Design Engineering

2020 - 2024

#### courses

engineering mathematics, mechanics, electronics, human-centred & industrial design, FEA, data science, python, javascript, robotics, sustainable design

### group projects:

the ambio brace – an ankle stabiliser for elderly users to avoid them twisting their ankles the U Me – a two-way communication device for severely autistic, non-verbal children

#### The Henrietta Barnett School - A Levels

2013 - 2020

3 A\* in Product Design, Mathematics and Further Mathematics, 1 A in History

# experience

# MathWorks - UX Design Intern

# July 2022 - September 2022

I worked as a UX Design Intern at The MathWorks, working on the redesign of the MATLAB interface. This included designing new features for MATLAB Desktop, as well as extending accessibility support for MATLAB Online. I worked on both the Parallel Computing and Deep Learning Toolboxes, designing for external MATLAB customers, as well as internal development teams.

# The Period Product Steriliser

# July 2021 - September 2021

Individually, I worked on a project working to alleviate period poverty in developing countries. After conducting a user-centric process, I designed a steriliser which could clean period products, meaning that they could be reused, leading to a long-lasting, hygienic supply.

# The Health Tracker App

### **July 2021 – September 2021**

Many young adults saw a reduction in their physical fitness as a result of the Covid-19 lockdowns. After speaking to them, I decided to design a health tracker app with which young adults were able to keep track of their meals and exercise habits. It was developed using C# and XAML.

# skills

### design skills

interview design usability testing personas journey mapping design ideation ergonomics

# design communication

adobe creative suite figma presentation design video editing

#### technical skills

mechanics
electronics
fea
robotics
data science
python
javascript
C++